roomstays.com 2014-06-17

# Privacy Policy - RoomStays.com

Privacy is extremely important to us. To give you better protection of your privacy, we are providing you this notice explaining our online practices regarding information as well as the implications of choices that you make regarding the method which your information is collected and used. The said notice will be applicable to all information that RoomStays.com is collecting or willingly submitted by the user to our website. So that you will not have any problems finding this page, we have located these policies in an area that is easy to find. We try to make these policies visible in our homepage as well as other areas where personal identifiable information is requested.

##### Information Collected

  * RoomStays.com may collate information about your visit in bulk that does not directly identify you or your experience. For instance, we may tell our investors regarding the number of hits (visits) our website has, or which destinations are popular.
  * RoomStays.com transacts business with adults and not children, and does not post or collect information about children.
  * The website server recognizes the pages and domain names that have been visited as a part of the data gathering in order to enhance each experience on the website.
  * In order to make and confirm your reservation, we need the following details: name, email address, physical address, credit card number, expiration date, billing address, and phone / fax number. We make it a point not to share these personal information with other parties except when necessary to make transactions complete.
  * RoomStays.com will be using the information that you are providing about yourself in order to enhance or improve the RoomStays.com website and make it as customer friendly as much as possible. We want to know you better to be able to make our services as best as possible. We do not desire to invade your life. There may be circumstances where we will be asking for a little bit more information about your travel interests and inclinations, but these are just performed to enhance our services. In the future, this information may be used by the company to make better travel recommendations that would suit your taste. However, this information is optional and you can choose not to provide it.
  * Email for email newsletters
  * The contact information you are asked to provide is needed in order to make all lines of communication open in the event that possible difficulties or other obstacles are faced during the processing of your requests or product order. In some instances, actual paper tickets may need to be mailed to you. Take note that the easier we are able to contact you, the better we can give you service.
  * If you would like to opt out of future emails, please unsubscribe securely at <https://www.roomstays.com/unsubscribe/>

##### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that is stored in your computer about you during your visit to websites. For our website, we use session ID cookies as well as persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, you just need to close the browner and the cookie terminates itself. On the other hand, the persistent cookie (a small text file stored in your computer), will stay in your computer for a period of time, or until you remove it. We use cookies to track the path the customer takes when browsing the website. The use of cookies is not liked to any personally identifiable information that the customer discloses while visiting your website.

##### Logged Information

The information that we use to analyze the trends is the customer's IP addresses. This also allows us to monitor the movements of the users as well as to effectively administer the website. This opens doors to broad demographic information, and other statistics. The IP addresses, however, are not liked to personally identifiable information.

##### Credit Card Processing

RoomStays.com uses the services of a credit card processing company as well as a bank check processing company to take care of the billings of users for the services and goods that he or she has availed of. These companies do not store, share, retain, or use the personally identifiable information for secondary purposes.

##### Media

In addition to our cookies, a cookie file may also be placed by some of our third party companies. These companies often use these cookies when gathering statistics about your visits to our website as well as other websites in order to provide you advertisements that are travel-related which you may be interested in. the information that they collect, does not in any way include your personal information.

The third party companies may also apply technology that is used to ensure the effectiveness of their ads. This is often accomplished through the utilization of a web beacon, which is placed on your site to collect anonymous information.

##### Disclaimer

Although we go through great lengths to ensure that user privacy is preserved, there may be instances required by law that we disclose information you have provided when you obtained our travel services and products. We may also disclose some of these information against somebody who poses a threat to our best interests, like customer fraud, or whose activities are damaging to the company. It may also be necessary for the company to disclose personal information in order to protect itself, or in instances where disputes need to be resolved.

##### Notification

If RoomStays.com makes necessary changes to its Privacy Policy, we will be updating the said page so that you are always aware of the information that we are collecting and how we are using this information. If at any point we shall start using personally identifiable information in a manner that is different from the one stated at the time it was collected, we shall be sending you an email regarding these changes. You will then have a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this new method.
